
// Array of objects
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Select the most appropriate synonym of the given word -Fleeting',
        options: ['Transient','Transparent','Tranquil','Tepid'],
        answer: 'Transient'
      },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Select the most appropriate synonym of the given word-Guile",
        options:['Honest',' Hot','Chicanery','Charming'],
        answer: 'Chicanery'
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:'Select the most appropriate antonym of the given word-Unholy',
        options:['Pity',' Impious',' Pave','Venerate'],
        answer: 'Venerate'
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:'Select the most appropriate antonym of the given word-Lax',
        options:['Firm','Careless',' Loot','Fiction'],
        answer: 'Firm'
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:'Select the wrongly spelt word.',
        options:['dangerous','skillful',' beautiful','vaccum'],
        answer: 'vaccum'
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:'Select the wrongly spelt word.',
        options:[' knoty',' haughty','vagabond','yolk'],
        answer: ' knoty'
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:'Fuddy-duddy',
        options:['An old fashioned and foolish type of person','A mental institutional facility','To become serious about something',' A wise person'],
        answer: 'An old fashioned and foolish type of person'
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:'Milk and water',
        options:['To be physically strong','Lacking the will or ability','To be very partial','To criticize somebody'],
        answer: 'Lacking the will or ability'
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:'Feel blue',
        options:['Feeling ecstatic','In trouble/depressed','An easy achievement','None of these'],
        answer: 'In trouble/depressed'
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:'Flies off at a tangent',
        options:['Self praising','To boast',' Start discussing something irrelevant','Well informed'],
        answer: ' Start discussing something irrelevant'
    },
]